{
    "subject": "Esperanza_Baur",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "John_Wayne",
    "human_readable": "Esperanza Baur is married to John Wayne.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9243857264518738,
            "question": "Who is Esperanza Baur married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8684589862823486,
            "question": "Name a famous actor married to Esperanza Baur."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7704628705978394,
            "question": "Is John Wayne married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7523709535598755,
            "question": "What is the name of Esperanza Baur's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7145001888275146,
            "question": "Is Esperanza Baur's husband widely recognized?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6629964709281921,
            "question": "Who is John Wayne's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6577773094177246,
            "question": "To whom is Esperanza Baur connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39809349179267883,
            "question": "Is Esperanza Baur known for being an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33586692810058594,
            "question": "What profession does John Wayne have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17524871230125427,
            "question": "Can you name a famous movie starring John Wayne?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Esperanza Baur is married to John Wayne.",
            "html": "yago_25936_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does John Wayne have?",
            "html": "yago_25936_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Esperanza Baur known for being an actress?",
            "html": "yago_25936_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Esperanza Baur connected?",
            "html": "yago_25936_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25936_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention Esperanza Baur as the wife of John Wayne on multiple occasions, specifically stating that they got married in 1946 and were married for six years before divorcing in 1952. This confirms that Esperanza Baur is indeed married to John Wayne."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Esperanza Baur was married to the actor John Wayne, supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}